Get back here, offering!
It's only a matter of time
until my target dies.
Super complete.
Is he gonna hit me with the Sound Masters'
Modified Bloodline Increment?
He was just bluffing
so he could run away?
Where is it?
If I find it before he does...
I super win this fight.
Those who ceaselessly hone
their killing arts are known as "Masters."
After many generations,
they have gained lethal abilities
called "Modified Bloodlines."
This is the story of one such Master,
the Sound Master, Genya Naruko,
and his super search for healing.
Locked in Latata
Secrets in my veins Latata
I know you want it
And sure, I love it
So I stay behind the mask Latata
Run, run, run back to back Run
Fun, fun, fun unpredictable but fun
At the end of every mind game
Shoot through the darkened night
Poisoned in our bodies still
Laugh at us our reckless souls
TOXIC
For you I will
Rewrite my destiny
Losing it, falling for you
What's tomorrow Kill or Kiss
TOXIC
Tell me what you want
I'll stay right here
Like a spell, I'll be by your side
What you gonna do Kill or Kiss
Kill or Kiss
You're cruel, Poison Master.
Even if my target survives
and becomes CEO,
her troubles will only get worse.
Her relatives will resent her.
Human scum will try to tear her down.
The responsibility's too heavy for her.
My target's too fragile for competition.
A weakling getting a taste of the world
of the strong super ends in tragedy.
She may have room to grow
and may super work her butt off.
But in the world of the strong,
people who are weak right now
cannot survive.
Foolhardy courage wears them down
and destroys them.
Super weak people are better off
living in nice, safe cages without-
Hey, Naruko.
Are you scared?
You ought to know how tough
Ureshino really is better than I do.
You amped-up her trauma,
and she still beat it on her own.
She's set out to conquer
her own weaknesses.
Maybe that makes her tougher than guys
like us, who got forced to be strong.
We're on super different
wavelengths, you and I.
I finally found it.
A super perfect healing spot!
Phytoncides. Healing compounds
that trees release into the air.
The Sound Masters' art isn't made
for hand-to-hand combat.
To play notes that will hook
my audience comprised of my enemy,
I need to be in peak condition.
As such, a forest
is my ideal battleground.
The phytoncides will let me
fight to my fullest.
No! Better than my fullest!
A hollow filled with phytoncides
has the potential to push me
to super new heights!
Ah.
It feels...
incredible.
The super most, super best,
super bliss I've ever felt.
I control every sound in this forest
and bring super certain death.
Modified Bloodline++:
Kannon.
These aren't phytoncides.
It just smells similar.
Poison gas?
He predicted what my technique required,
set a trap, and drove me here?
But I haven't lost yet.
If I spit out the poison and move away-
Water-absorbent polymer?
Sound Master, you're great at what you do,
but moves as complicated as yours
must have special requirements.
Just like I shave time off my life
to power up, you had to need healing.
Phytoncides.
Mixing a poisonous gas with that stuff
was a first, and it wasn't easy,
but tricks like this...
are more my specialty
than throwing punches.
Poison Master,
I've super got to thank you...
for buying into my lies.
Why isn't Kinosaki picking up?
Taking me down...
won't stop the hysteria.
We're out of options.
Who's youngest after Ureshino?
Ureshino! There's an old track into town
on the west side of the village.
A-Actually, Ms. Kinosaki...
I'm going back.
To where everyone is.
Are you out of your mind?
They might kill you!
You need to get away before it's too-
I can't!
If I just save myself,
they'll sacrifice someone else instead.
I'll leave everyone with scars that
will hurt them their whole lives. So...
I have an idea.
Sorry, Osawa. We're doing this
to placate Lord Chladni.
We need you to stand in for Ureshino!
Please wait.
What now?
There she is.
It's Ureshino.
Grab her!
Wake up, Flame Devil.
Don't worry, everybody.
I'll use my powers
to exorcise Lord Chladni.
When you speak to a crowd of people,
relax your body and speak from the belly.
If you worry you're going too slow,
that's the right pace.
And use this perfume.
It's a hit with men and women.
I wear it all the time.
Thank you so much.
You didn't have to go along
with me like this.
I'm helping because I think you can do it.
At least, the way you are now.
But if it doesn't work, run. Okay?
R-Right.
It'll be fine. I can do this. I can.
Now...
Hold it!
You expect us to believe
you can get rid of Lord Chladni?
Osawa?
You've just been running scared
because you don't want to get sacrificed!
Yeah!
All bark, no bite.
If you're that strong,
why didn't you exorcise him sooner?
Do you want us all to die?
How could you?
Coward!
I was waiting for my energy to build up.
That's why I came back on my own.
Th-Then, exorcise him, if you can!
Do it now!
I want to run. I'm scared. I want to
go home. How'd I end up in this mess?
I'm gonna throw up. I've had enough.
I'm not cut out for this. I'm tired.
If they find out I'm bluffing now,
someone will pay the price for sure.
It'll ruin all their lives.
I won't let that happen.
Flame Devil, are you ready?
You want me to blow gas on it
when you give the signal?
Y-Yes. It's all dead leaves,
so I think it'll burn.
I know I'm asking a lot of you.
No, it's no big deal.
You're the one with the hard job.
You've got to make them believe
your party tricks are real magic.
Flame Devil! Burst!
There! Lord Chladni has, uh, passed on.
So, now, um...
How about we all build a campfire?
Yeah? So it worked?
I'll be right with you.
You dealt me a super total defeat.
Like hell I did. You lost to Ureshino.
To Ureshino, who's overcoming
her own weakness.
I see.
What are you waiting for? Finish him.
The weak are fated to die sooner or later.
Dying at his little brother's hands
is the best he can hope for.
I've never been strong.
Super not even once.
Why don't you finish me off?
Today's a special day.
It's orientation, remember?
Naruko, if you want to to be healed
from the bottom of your heart,
why don't you try opening up
to someone about your weakness?
Poison Master Hikaru Gero.
It's super none of your business.
Mr. Gero.
So this is a campfire?
I've heard the legends.
Gero.
Ureshino says she's got a present for you.
I'm not sure you'll like it, though.
A Supersize Mixy-Max Mix Kit!
Even with a fight to the death, that's
the most damage you've taken all day.
You just don't get it, Kinosaki.
This is a historic event!
The world record for biggest DIY candy kit
hasn't been broken in 22 years,
and this one just blew it
out of the water!
Yes, yes.
G-Good morning, everybody.
It's almost time for breakfast.
I had the weirdest dream.
Me, too.
Ureshino was really a witch,
and she fought a monster.
She was descended from onmyoji.
No, she was an elite spirit medium.
I, uh, I'm just good at magic tricks.
It looks like our ride's here.
Thank you so much, Mr. Gero.
You saved me and
you smoothed everything over.
All I did was put a heavy filter
on their memories.
Hey, what gives?
Oh, sorry. I wasn't thinking.
I picked up patting people's heads
when I praise them from my dad.
Pat away, Ureshino.
Gero needs to get used to compliments.
There, there.
Thanks to you, no one had to
feel sad, or hurt, or resentful,
and I got to make the best memories ever!
I'll take pride in getting
to know you as long as I live.
G-Great.
Anyway, don't you think that's enough?
Don't forget Kinosaki.
Not nearly enough!
And I already patted Ms. Kinosaki.
We got it out of the way
while you weren't looking.
(Together With Me)
And so, I can't accept payment.
I'll super return the full amount.
Now, guess I'll get going.
I'll be super first in the bath
and super refreshed in every way.
Don't give me that crap!
The Sound Master dropped the ball! Shit!
Good thing you hired me, then, huh?
Me and my partner here
will blow her into paste.
You're the only one left.
What? What do you want?
My life? Or my fortune?
Just one thing.
Please train me like hell!
I want to do the kind of work
that takes all the gloom in the world
and blows it away.
But I...
I know.
Balzak means more to you than life itself.
You worked yourself to the bone
under my dad to make it as big as it is.
It's up to you whether you accept my will.
But...
If Shiori shows promise,
I want you to look out for her.
So...
I want you to liven up the company
together with me!
Please?
I'll train you like hell.
I warn you, I'm as strict as the devil.
Mr. Gero, Ms. Kinosaki...
Huh?
W-Wait a second, Gero!
What?
Are you sure?
You didn't get Ureshino's contact info.
I'd only dealt with human garbage before,
so it wasn't until I met Ureshino
and Himekawa that it finally hit me.
This world of ours
isn't as grimy as I thought.
Getting married isn't what
Ureshino needs right now.
A guy like me will only get in her way.
I thought through how I'd make her feel,
and that's what I decided.
...thinking through how things
make them feel.
Nice going, Gero.
I believed you and Ureshino
could've hit it off.
But we'll pick ourselves up
and move on to-
P-Please wait.
There's still something that
I-no, that both of us haven't done...
that we haven't overcome yet!
Please join me for
one last drinking party.
Have you all got something to drink?
Ready to go.
Yeah.
Okay, then. Let's get started!
Cheers!
Mr. Gero, did you see this week's Ropes?
Ropes?
Ropes, short for Twisted Ropes.
On every Sunday night at 10:30.
Sorry.
The other day...
I rode a shark.
A shark? really?
Shark. Same. Chompsky. Kinosaki rode him,
too. Shark fin. I thought I was a goner.
Make some conversation!
They suck at talking! I mean, I knew that.
And they're from completely different
worlds with nothing in common.
This is hard mode.
They had no problem
talking on the camping trip,
but now they have the perfect chance,
they can't think of anything to say.
A rift will grow between them
if this keeps up.
This looks bad.
I've been keeping quiet,
but they leave me no choice.
I'll take charge for now.
Listen, you two-
Let me...
show you a new party trick
I came up with.
Another party trick? After last time?
If the mood gets any more hellish,
even I won't be able to-
I'd...
I'd like to see that.
What are you going to do, Gero?
Spew liquid DIY candy out of your mouth?
Please don't ruin your chances
with Ureshino.
Hey, it matches my scarf.
And my favorite flowers!
I thought all a party trick
had to do was get attention.
But I guess I was wrong.
You taught me that.
The key is to face people head-on
and entertain them.
Mr. Gero.
I thought up a new trick, too.
I'd like to show it off.
They suck at talking, but if they can
communicate like this, so what?
I had a great time.
Same here.
So I guess, uh...
Be the best CEO you can.
I will.
I won't see you again, will I?
Well, my mission's complete.
I'm greedy, you know?
There are so many things I want to do.
And I don't want to neglect
Balzak or college at all.
Or falling in love, either.
Mr. Gero! Thank you for the other day!
Shiori, I'm here to drive you home.
Mr. Gero, thank you so much for tonight.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Would you mind adding me as a friend?
I'd like to see you again.
I planned out 65,536 scenarios
for getting him to add me,
but it still almost gave me
a heart attack.
(Friends)
Is Ureshino into me,
or was she just being polite?
Who can say?
Well, don't rush things and just focus
on developing your relationship.
Right.
Okay.
Let's begin our next operation on Sunday.
I can't do that day.
How come? Got other plans?
Yeah.
A friend's wedding.
Ah! Something smells fishy!
I'm shocked, startled,
it's adding insult to injury
I'm completely obsessed
Ah! Something smells off!
You're all bluff,
I'm sick and tired, so disappointed
Bye-bye, mwah!
It seems like I'm only good at
workbooks for a child
Even through infectious disease,
I want to love with you
No! No! Love's in gridlock!
Forever and ever, I love you,
Shake Na Baby
Darling, heading toward a twisted signpost
Heart fluttering, I love you,
Shake Na Baby
Just the two of us, consolation prize
Ah, the scent of dance
I'm completely obsessed
with you as you flutter down
Ah, something smells off
I'm blown away by you
Bye-bye, mwah!
It seems like I'm only good at
workbooks for a child
I want us to share even our growing pains
No! No! Love's in gridlock!
Forever and ever, I love you,
Shake Na Baby
Darling, heading toward
a stagnant signpost
Heart fluttering, I love you,
Shake Na Baby
Singing a grand chorus cheekily
Do you think I can pull off
a marriage that perfect?
I promise
I'll find one for you.
Leave.
Next time: "The Bug Master's Wedding."